Just wanted to quickly touch on programming and debugging.
That's getting rid of the little beastly bugs that come into your program and solving problems.
Programming is a is a very sort of iterative process.
It means you've got to go around and around.
You make mistakes.
You you have to figure it out.
And that's what makes it exciting.
It's sort of like a problem solving process.
And so you do need to keep trying.
And as you as you go through the course, you will see that we'll give you examples where we actually
get it wrong on purpose, so we can show you and how you solve things.
Now you're going to learn a lot in this course, but guaranteed absolutely 100%.
They're going to be things that you're going to try that just don't seem to work like we told you.
The option then is to now reach out to someone.
And the lovely thing is Google is there.
Google, you can just come here and say, please help me.
And Google will just like, okay, no, right.
Maybe that won't help you.
You've got to be a little bit more specific.
You can simply just Google literally whatever it is.
Say you've got a Python query about something.
Now one of the places we find that is really good is Stack Overflow.
You can just Google Stack Overflow and you'll find it.
In fact, Google will bring you straight to Stack Overflow and allow you to type in a a search just
on that site.
So Stack Overflow is where with lots of clever people, share ideas, ask questions, get answers.
So, for example, we mentioned earlier that sometimes when you install wing 101, it's using the wrong
Python version.
Just to give you an example.
So if I said wing 101 wrong Python version and went to Stack Overflow, it's going to come up with a
whole lot of options.
Here we go.
Configure Python 3.32 from that I could read that and you probably are going to find your answer here.
So basically all these different well sites or links that come up are questions that people have asked.
So you'll notice that if you search anything, even on Stack Overflow, almost every single question
has been asked.
If you have a problem, there's a huge chance that someone else has had the exact same problem.
So with programming, if you have a question, don't just go on to one of these sites and type in your
question and wait for someone to answer you.
Programmers get very annoyed if you haven't put in the research and haven't actually tried to find the
answer before asking someone.
Yeah, but a lot of these questions have come up over and over.
I mean, this was asked four years ago, so just make sure you have fully researched your problem and
if you really cannot find a solution, then put it out on onto one of these sites.
What's also really nice about sites like Stack Overflow is answers get voted up depending on how good
they are.
So you'll see if our answers got more likes or whatever.
It goes up higher.
So it obviously work for more people.
So if you can't find the answer anywhere here, you've searched the whole site.
You're really not getting it right.
Then by all means, you know, hit ask a question and type in your own question.
So the bottom line is you are going to be having to reach out to people.
But in our modern Google world, with so many experts connected, you guaranteed are going to find your
answer.
You're not.
Whatever problem you've had, you can be certain someone else had that same problem, so be prepared
for that.
Just go out there, search and before you know it, you're going to get an answer to your question.
That's part of the adventure.
And that's where the learning lies in learning lies in making mistakes and then correcting them.
And what's exciting is there's so many people out there, and of course, we're more than happy.
If you want to reach out to us, ask us a question.
We'd be happy to help as well.
But as you move forward, as you get more and more powerful and incredible and clever, you're going
to want to spread your wings.
That's a pun.
Yeah, spread your wings and search the great wide web for answers to your questions.